<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Connor-Jay&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Connor-Jay&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BinaryShield: a bin2bin x86-64 code virtualizer</title>
      <link>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/binaryshield-a-bin2bin-x86-64-code-virtualizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/binaryshield-a-bin2bin-x86-64-code-virtualizer/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this post is primarily to explain the technical workings of my tool, BinaryShield, but it can also be treated as an introduction to VM based protections.&#xA;This is NOT About Hypervisor Technology! To clear up any confusion, I want to first clarify that we are not talking about hypervisors such as VMware. I cannot stress that enough. Although they share similar ideas and terminology, I would argue that the kind of VM, or virtual machine, we will be discussing in the post is completely different to hypervisor technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Clemson University</title>
      <link>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/hacking-clemson-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://connorjaydunn.github.io/blog/posts/hacking-clemson-university/</guid>
      <description>This article details the steps I took to discover and exploit an SQL injection vulnerability on the Clemson University website using my own tool, SQLiF (SQL injection Finder).&#xA;DISCLAIMER This post and the release of my tool, SQLiF, are intended for educational purposes only. I was previously granted permission from Clemson University to document and share my findings with others. I am not responsible for anything you do with the information presented within this post.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
